[
    
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Pick out the infinitive from the given sentence. - I was scolded and asked to clean the room.",
        "options":
        [
            "Scolded",
            "Asked",
            "To clean",
            "Clean"
        ],
        "correctAns": "To clean"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Pick out two compound words - 1.makeup 2.make brake 3.walking stick  4.walk slow ",
        "options":
        [
            "1 and 2",
            "1 and 3",
            "1 and 4",
            "None"
        ],
        "correctAns": "1 and 3"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Find out 2 hidden words of minimum 4 letters from downwards - 1.and 2.down 3.ward 4.dward     5.Rads",
        "options":
        [
            "1 and 2",
            "2 and 3",
            "3 and 4",
            "4 and 5"
        ],
        "correctAns": "2 and 3"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Choose the correct sentence from the following sentence.",
        "options":
        [
            "Is that so. said Shiva.",
            "is that so? Said shiva.",
            "is that so? said Shiva.",
            "Is that so? said Shiva."
        ],
        "correctAns": "Is that so? said Shiva."
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Identify the kinds of sentence. - Then he flapped his wings and he soared upwards.",
        "options":
        [
            "Simple  sentence",
            "Compound sentence",
            "Complex sentence",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Compound sentence"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Complete the words by using correct letters in the blank. - 1. Compa_y, 2.mista_e, 3.wor_d, 4. g_al ",
        "options":
        [
            "e, t, r, o",
            "n, t, l, o",
            "n, l, t, o",
            "t, r, o, e"
        ],
        "correctAns": "n, t, l, o"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Spot the error in the following sentence and rewrite it.- One of my friend is a great footballer.",
        "options":
        [
            "One",
            "my",
            "friend",
            "footballer"
        ],
        "correctAns": "friend"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Arrange the following words in alphabetical order. - comatos, comb, comagmatic, comanche.",
        "options":
        [
            "1234",
            "1432",
            "4321",
            "3412"
        ],
        "correctAns": "3412"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"Complete the following word-chain of adjectives. - Beautiful, L________, _________",
        "options":
        [
            "Luxurious, Suitable",
            "Last, trouble",
            "Long, gone",
            "Live, entry"
        ],
        "correctAns": "Luxurious, Suitable"
    },
    {
        "QorL":"Q",
        "question":"He had won his laurels in athletic events. (Indentify the tense)",
        "options":
        [
            "Simple Present Tense.",
            "Past Perfect Tense.",
            "Past continuous Tense.",
            "Past Perfect Continuous Tesne."
        ],
        "correctAns": "Past Perfect Tense."
    }
]